Hello, hello friends, welcome to dinner today in
this video series in which we talk about it.
This is our series in
which we match suggestions like two or three
pistachios and we do fundamental research on them
and see which subscribe
[laughter]
[music]
subscribe. Keep watching this video and
subscribe to the appointed person.
Here, first of all, we want to tell you
which company we are today, in
which the completion will take place. So, this company
subscribe to our team,
subscribe to our channel,
Om Shanti dot capital structure channel, star
and difficulty does it.
First of all, let's apply the plate. Not
only this, we want to know what happens with toys. So
friends, please subscribe to the channel, which
means that the company, because there is
no benefit in subscribing. So,
watch this here and subscribe to
our Ghagra subscribe to
generate the explanation and it
shows the office collection of the company.
After that, our third one will be from this, it will show
that subscribe does not make any difference, so
here  Those who subscribe
and subscribe, so subscribe to this, on the
one hand they make many efforts for the Green Team, so
it comes negative because you
will see that their statue is coming in 2009,
so subscribe, subscribe
[music]
subscribe, subscribe,
Shravan is engaged in his third attempt,
enterprise value of policies,
in this we will decide, subscribe to the company,
but subscribe here you can see
our Ghagra, subscribe to this channel in the market,
and if
we divide it by this, then
which part of it will be ours, so we have to
comment, we
calculate for both the companies one by one,
first of all we calculate, as you can
see, here we have written the face,
like the performance of the team,
subscribe, subscribe, so let me
tell you this here, I have done it in the background, so
type subscribe and collect it from the tehsil,
now if we cut it, then it comes
1968, so as I told you that the
company has subscribed, so here we
get subscribe and subscribe, so here
you will go to your office, you will
subscribe and appoint  But you are
seeing 1518 subscribers, you
can check this from any website. So now let's go to
our app and I've
updated it in our app, it becomes
one and two, and right now our green 3gp
is New India Assurance Company Limited,
it is leading, ICICI Lombard
General Insurance Company Limited. So now we'll
go to our second round, which is the channel
subscription to
[music],
our second round is the bottom line, in this
we talk about the bottom line, that is, the
area below the dream, subscribe,
subscribe, share,
and if it is not like this, then we
subscribe, and the second thing we have to check
for that is what is the
net profit percentage from our
next, so what we have to do with this, this shows the
operational efficiency of the company,
and the third one is the profit
margin, this shows from the side of the company how much
it earns in purchasing its products
from the market, so subscribe all these things
here, you can see 200
subscribers and this  If we do something then
here we
select China because they have
one thing pages net profit and
select it and now we go to our
second subscribe, in the first place
you will see that our channel
subscribe and do this thing, here
also the team has won, so we will select
and we subscribe to Next
9 News Room,
today we are taking its average, it goes to
65.30 percent and if we
can do it for creative then it comes to
65.73.4%, Preeti has gone ahead by a few points
here and our
second one becomes their growth,
routine to pause and printing point and now
we update it
in our angle, so let's go
to the board and we update the blue team suit
price of dream team one point, Maharaj
overall score gets three, right
now both the companies got protein stars
and are standing at par, our second
work is over and we will move to the third round,
our third round is valuable system
And there will be two points in it, let's see
what happens, it's not just basically
one, it prevents anyone from buying this experiment,
whether the
value of this is interview and we have the
value of buying the same, so here we
appoint someone for this, the
second one is the one which we
subscribe to,
soon let's see which
company provides the facility, so here we are
looking at the first victim for routine, so
here we are submitting it, it is
coming 60 and if we click on this thing, then the
lower one here will be our
subscribe and second one is and for this
we subscribe, subscribe and
subscribe,
quoting it, where
we use GPS growth, its length, then
our victim will come, so here
we will cut it for both the companies, the
things we need here,
this is our rotting hormone,
more last point and now we will cut it,
these things we need as
war subscribe, subscribe and here we
subscribe
APPSC, so it comes  28.12 and you will do it
in pink plots, in this we put the name
of the company and subscribe for it,
subscribe is written and that is there, so we
subscribe here and
subscribe, subscribe
Loot Current Affairs Current Affairs inch from
here 15 750 last year's justice GPS
3.67 so we will cut these in the same way, we will take
it out and the one in his village is
tremendous 138, so now we divide these
and subscribe, so here he is
sitting here and subscribe to this channel,
here one
mosque we put our mails
in the board and our overall score goes,
you have seen that there is a tremendous
competition going on here, the
problem of both the companies is that we have time because
on this channel we have to subscribe to it,
this is the combination,
we do about it here, so for this we subscribe a lot, so here
we
subscribe that ghee 50 subscribe and this, so
subscribe and these two,
in a glance it wins, the
rating gets one  Want to follow team
gets 0.5 inch and if we update it then
you will see that here our
Preeti has won the race i.e.
New India Assurance Company whose
share icon is 20 then subscribe to this channel
and subscribe how did you like this video, if
you liked the video then please
like and share it and if you have not subscribed then
please subscribe to our channel
thank you